<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Sasha Sax</title>
    <link>https://alexsax.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Sasha Sax</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Sasha Sax</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alexsax.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Locality Prior</title>
      <link>https://alexsax.github.io/project/locality-prior/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsax.github.io/project/locality-prior/</guid>
      <description>FMRI images of the brain reveal that there is significant neuronal clustering of activations. It is believed that these correlated activations indicate areas of the brain with functional specificity. These areas function at various levels of abstraction, from low-level sensorimotor tasks, to mid-level identification of faces, and even very abstract things such as thinking about another&amp;rsquo;s thoughts [2]. The brain has specific activation patterns in response to different visual inputs, and the object being viewed can be decoded from these patterns [3].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flame Wars: Automatic Insult Detection</title>
      <link>https://alexsax.github.io/project/insult-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsax.github.io/project/insult-detection/</guid>
      <description>Toxic comments are increasingly drowning out constructive ones, and websites are reacting by shutting down comment sections. Human moderation is slow and expensive, so an algorithmic solution would be preferable. In this project, we explore the problem, existing literature, and recurrent models that have not yet been applied to this task.
Character LSTMs offer a robust solution because they capture semantics while being robust to typos and intentional obfuscations. Because of this, they hold a significant advantage over common filtering tequniques such as wordlists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SALTIER</title>
      <link>https://alexsax.github.io/project/text-summarization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsax.github.io/project/text-summarization/</guid>
      <description>Effective text summarization has the potential to allow people to process more information. To further this goal, we present multiple extractive baselines on the NYT dataset, which is a large dataset that immediately yields real-life applications. These baselines combine state-of-the-art techniques from many different sources and provide a solid starting point for further work using this hitherto untapped resource.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>